♪ She would never say
where she came from ♪
♪ Yesterday don't matter
if it's gone ♪
♪ While the sun is bright ♪
♪ Or in the darkest night ♪
♪ No one knows ♪
♪ She comes and goes ♪
♪ Goodbye, Ruby Tuesday ♪
♪ Who could hang
a name on you? ♪
♪ When you change with
every new day ♪
♪ Still, I'm gonna miss you ♪
♪ Don't question why
she needs to be so free ♪
♪ She'll tell you
it's the only way to be ♪
♪ She just can't be chained ♪
♪ To a life where
nothing's gained ♪
♪ And nothing's lost ♪
♪ At such a cost ♪
♪ Goodbye, Ruby Tuesday ♪
♪ Who could hang
a name on you? ♪
♪ When you change with
every new day ♪
♪ Still, I'm gonna miss you ♪
♪ "There's no time to lose,"
I heard her say ♪
♪ Catch your dreams
before they slip away ♪
♪ Dying all the time ♪
♪ Lose your dreams
and you will lose your mind ♪
♪ Ain't life unkind? ♪
♪ Goodbye, Ruby Tuesday ♪
♪ Who could hang
a name on you? ♪
♪ When you change with
every new day ♪
♪ Still, I'm gonna miss you ♪
♪ Goodbye, Ruby Tuesday ♪
♪ Who could hang
a name on you? ♪
♪ When you change with
every new day ♪
♪ Still, I'm gonna miss you ♪
[♪♪♪♪♪]